Contact

shereenichole@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shereepritchard-polly-bsn-rn-750b90173 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals Patient Safety

Sheree Pritchard-Polly BSN, RN

Nurse Manager at HCA Healthcare

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Pediatric and Emergency Department experienced Registered Nurse with over eight years of experience.

Influential leader and loyal team player with an unwavering commitment to providing safe quality patient care. Strong delegator of nursing assignments, scheduling, admissions and discharges oversight, patient monitoring and cost management.

Experience

HCA Healthcare

5 years 7 months

Nurse Manager-PICU/Pedi
January 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Support Assistant Vice President of Operations with daily operational functions.

Assist in the development of new rapid response documentation form.

Collaborate with unit leaders to ensure exceptional care delivery.

Perfrom monthly rounding on each employee.

Review and report Press Ganey scores weekly.

Participate in charge nurse certification program. Anticipated Completion Date, November 2018.

Collaborate with unit leaders in the development of the content for the annual skills fair.

Manage productivity and payroll to align with department budget.

Manage scheduling and staffing needs of the unit.

Perform daily narcotic audits.

Assisted in the development of employee engagement action plan.

Interim Nurse Manager-PICU/Pedi March 2018 - January 2019 (11 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Assistant Nurse Manager-PICU/Pedi November 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 5 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Supervise staff in a 32 mixed PICU/Pediatric Medical-Surgical Unit.

Manage productivity and payroll to align with department budget.

Holds staff accountable for performing hourly rounding validations and bedside rounding validations.

Complete nurse leader rounds each shift.

Maintain an exceptional level of patient care.

Perform annual evaluations on nursing and non-nursing staff.

Collaborated on the creation of a PICU electronic handoff tool.

Serve as an educational resource for nurses.

Collaborated and planned in the startup and development of new pediatric center in a non-pediatric

facility.

Ensure exceptional care delivery by building solid, trusting relationships with staff and patient families.

Monitor employee compliance with attendance policy, medication scanning, and incremental overtime.

Collaborate with all members of interdisciplinary team, therapists, social workers, doctors, and pharmacists.

Franciscan Missionaries of Our Lady Health System Charge Nurse/Staff Nurse-Emergency Department March 2012 - November 2014 (2 years 9 months)

Monroe, Louisiana Area

Assessed, planned, implemented, evaluated, and documented nursing care for patients experiencing

life-threatening problems requiring complex assessments, high-intensity therapies and interventions in a

32-bed Emergency Services Department. Supervised Registered Nurses, Licensed Practical Nurses, paramedics, certified nursing assistants, and unit secretaries.

Collaborated with all members of a interdisciplinary team of therapists, social workers, doctors, and

pharmacists. Served as an educational resource for nurses. Maintained an exceptional level of patient care.

Merit Health

Staff Registered Nurse- Women & Children Services September 2010 - March 2012 (1 year 7 months)

Vicksburg, Mississippi

Education

American Sentinel University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2017 - 2018)

American Sentinel University

Master of Science - MS, Nursing Administration · (2019)

Hinds Community College
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse